incu.com 2019-11-13

# Privacy | Incu

The following privacy policy applies to the products and services provided online exclusively by Incu Pty. Ltd. ABN 18 099 484 527 – Suite 5.09, 77 Dunning Ave, Rosebery, NSW 2018, Australia. The terms ‘we’, ‘our’, ‘us’ and ‘site’ refer to incu.com, Incu Pty. Ltd. and all of its related entities.

This Privacy Policy is written in accordance with the Privacy Act 1988 (Cth) (Privacy Act) and details the way in which Incu collects, stores and uses information that you provide to us.

## Collection of your personal information

Incu collects personal information from our online visitors when they place an order or when they join the Incu mailing list. If an order is placed, Incu holds personal information including your name, email address, phone number/s, shipping and billing address to process and fulfil the order.

Your credit card details will never be held by Incu.

In certain circumstances Incu may be required to collect and store additional data. Incu will only do this with your consent. These details allow Incu to process your order and to let you know the status of your order.

You may refuse to provide us with some or all of your personal information, however this may prevent us from processing your transactions or delivering products to you.

Incu may also need to obtain information for authentication or identity checks in the prevention of fraud. These measures are taken for your security.

## What we might use your personal information for

Incu will likely use your personal information for the processing of orders, payments and to provide you with a personalised shopping experience.

When you register with Incu, you will be asked if you want to “Subscribe” to our mailing list. If you choose to “Subscribe” for this service, the information you provide will allow incu to advise you about new products, special offers and other events or items of interest, from time to time.

Incu collates statistical information about site traffic, sales and other commercial information which might be passed on to trusted third parties however these statistics do not include any information which can identify you personally.

We might use your personal information for internal marketing and demographic studies, together with your non-personal data to monitor customer patterns in an effort to consistently improve the incu.com site for a better online shopping experience.

## Security of your personal information

Incu only collects personally identifiable information to the extent deemed reasonably necessary to serve you, in view of its legitimate business purposes as set out above, and we will do our best to maintain appropriate safeguards to ensure the security, integrity and privacy of the information you have provided.

When you place an order or access your account information, Incu uses a Secure Socket Layer (SSL) so your details are encrypted before being sent to us to protect them from unauthorised use.

## Third party

Incu may employ third party business partners to collect personal information. Please note that this Privacy Policy applies to Incu, but may not be relevant to websites maintained by other organisations to which there is a link on incu.com.

Incu recommends reading the policy and disclaimers published by any other organisations before submitting any personal information to them.

## Other information we might collect

Incu might collect non-personal data about your use of incu.com, such as pages visited, times and volume of use of our services as well as traffic data. Traffic data includes all sorts of boring things like logs, details of networks, time of log-on or access, length of sessions and similar systems data and your IP address. The information collected helps Incu to improve its online service to you

## Cookie Policy

We use cookies on our site to enhance and deliver a personalised shopping experience for you. A cookie is a small data file, stored on your computer or handheld device that enables us to track and target your preferences. The cookie will be held on your device until you remove it.

We may use cookies, or similar technology to track your use of the website or other sites related to our business partners. By using and/or browsing the Website, you consent to cookies being used in accordance with our policy. If you do not consent, you must disable cookies on your browser or refrain from using the Website.

## Accessing or updating your personal information

If personal information maintained by Incu is not correct you can easily update it using the “Log In” menu on the home page where your personal information will be made available, in the “My Account” section, for review and you can make any changes there.

## In or Out

If you would like to Unsubscribe from receiving emails from Incu you can do so by clicking the automated Unsubscribe link which is always included at the bottom of every email Incu sends or if you would like to be removed from the Incu database please contact us via the Contact Form here.

## Questions & Complaints

Incu may make changes to this Privacy Policy from time to time, without notice to you. The up-to-date version of our Privacy Policy is always available on our website.

## Changes to this policy

We would love to hear from you. If you would like to share something with us please call the Incu Customer Care Department on +61 (02) 9331 1014 or you might prefer to email us, please use the Contact Form.

Incu will be entitled to assume that if you have accessed the incu.com website you unconditionally accept the terms and conditions described in our Privacy Policy and in the absence of any contrary disclosure that you consent to this Policy.
